<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2024 Submissions on Waycrate</title><link>https://waycrate.github.io/outreach/gsoc/2024/submissions/</link><description>Recent content in 2024 Submissions on Waycrate</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://waycrate.github.io/outreach/gsoc/2024/submissions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Project 1 - Introduce DMA-BUF backend in Wayshot for high performance screen capture</title><link>https://waycrate.github.io/outreach/gsoc/2024/submissions/project-1-sooraj/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://waycrate.github.io/outreach/gsoc/2024/submissions/project-1-sooraj/</guid><description>Mentor: Zubair Mohammed
Student: Sooraj S
Original writeup is hosted at https://cheerfulpianissimo.github.io/notes/GSOC/GSOC.html</description></item><item><title>Project 2 - Improving the security model of swhkd</title><link>https://waycrate.github.io/outreach/gsoc/2024/submissions/project-2-ishan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://waycrate.github.io/outreach/gsoc/2024/submissions/project-2-ishan/</guid><description>Improving the security model of swhkd Mentors: Aakash Sen Sharma Student: Ishan Joshi Over the past few months, I have been working on a lot of different changes to the swhkd codebase. Me and my mentor together have gone through various approachs that could be used to simplify the swhkd codebase and also improve it&amp;rsquo;s security model. The journey has been thoroughly documented and ordered, including all of the mistakes that I made and the things that I learnt on this site itself.</description></item><item><title>Project 3 - Formalize SWHKD parser using regular grammar notation</title><link>https://waycrate.github.io/outreach/gsoc/2024/submissions/project-3-himadri/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://waycrate.github.io/outreach/gsoc/2024/submissions/project-3-himadri/</guid><description>Overview Hello and welcome to the final GSoC post for 2024! My task was to formalize the SWHKD parser using context-free EBNF notation. This post is to serve as a birdseye view of what I have developed over this summer.
Mentors: Aakash Sen Sharma Student: Himadri Bhattacharjee Report Architecting the parser I started out with the scaffolding of the parser in an extended Backus-Naur form garmmar template in a separate repository called SWEET using a Rust framework called pest.</description></item></channel></rss>